[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[2010 Haesol City Superintendent's Cup Judo Tournament]
[Sharp skills, strong mind! Go Haesol Judo Team! Haesol's pride is on the line!]
[Finals] [Haesol High Jung Woo Jae : Yoon Ha Ru]
What is this? Is it a dream?
2010?
Everyone in the center, please.
What? Is he talking to me?
Player Yoon Ha Ru, what are you doing?
Come on, onto the mat, please.
Why is he telling me that?
What is this?
Woo Jae!
Jung Woo Jae!
What is this?
Where am I?
Mom? Dad?
Jung Woo Jae?
Woo Jae!
- What the... - What is he doing?
- What? - Yoon Ha Ru?
- What's going on? - Ha Ru?
He's just nervous. That must be it.
- It's just nerves. - Surely, yeah.
Hey!
Start!
Woo Jae, full point!
Hey, Yoon Ha Ru.
You okay?
Wait, are you crying?
Huh?
No way.
Are you crying because you lost to me?
What?
What am I... doing over there?
What am I doing over there?
Where do you think you're touching, you bastard?
What the heck!
- Honey, come here, look! - Honey...
Ha Na is awake!
Ha Ru, too!
Ha Ru, Ha Ru!
Oh, thank goodness! Thank goodness!
Doctor! They're awake!
I'll go get someone, honey.
Nurse!
Ha Ru.
Ha Na.
Can you see me? It's Mom.
Mom...
Thank goodness, oh, good heavens!
Everything's going to be fine now that you're awake!
- Oh, my sweet children! - Mom...
Yes, darling? What is it?
Where is Woo Jae?
He was... with me just now.
Did you have a dream about him?
A dream?
Ha Na.
I'm sure Woo Jae is in a better place now.
He was a good boy.
That was a dream?
That was just a dream?
What's taking your dad so long anyway?
He's supposed to be back with a doctor by now.
I saw him, too.
Jung Woo Jae.
Do twins have matching dreams? Is that even a thing?
What a messed-up dream.
The dream...
It was so vivid.
I could hear him breathe up close.
I wish it lasted longer.
We could've had more time together.
I wish I never woke up.
Huh?
What?
Hey.
Yoon Ha Na.
What?
This is...
What is this?
What are you talking about?
It changed.
What did?
The medal!
I got the gold medal that day, right?
Now it's silver!
Huh?
What in the...
Did I... really do that?
Wait, that's...
That's me!
Huh?
Rewind it one more time.
So, what you're saying is...
that that wasn't actually a dream?
If it had been, how would the medal have changed?
And the video changed as well.
It mysteriously disappeared, too, right?
It's suspicious, no?
Maybe we're still dreaming?
I guess not.
It absolutely wasn't a dream.
How does that make any sense?
It makes no sense...
- Or does it? - Well, what if...
it does make sense?
Huh?
If we can go back in time,
and change the color of the medal...
Then...
Woo Jae.
Maybe we could do the same with him.
Wait, why isn't it working?
How do I do this?
Give it here.
Have you lost it? That thing's already old as bones!
Sorry.
Let's do a recap.
Okay.
We were on our way home...
When a truck hurtled our way.
Then the camcorder started playing back a video on its own.
That's everything I can recall.
Do you remember anything else?
I've got nothing after the truck.
I don't know what you want me to say.
And...
When I came to,
I was recording Woo Jae and me with the camcorder.
Well, not me, you.
Anyway...
I was recording. That's the point.
Then, I saw the match end in, what, 3 seconds with a full point.
There were tears, Woo Jae was confused...
Well, I thought it was all a dream. But something was clearly off.
So I was feeling myself up a little,
and felt something weird on my chest...
That's enough, I get it.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I was shocked, too, you know.
That's why I dropped the camcorder, and that was that.
And so we returned to the present, right?
- Ready? - Yeah.
Here goes.
One, two, three.
Dang it. It's not working.
Ow, my legs.
I guess your legs are too short to hurt, huh?
It's not working.
Dive in.
Dive in?
Okay. Sure...
No, hold on a little longer!
I almost drowned!
It looks... pretty deep, huh?
Well...
We need to jump at the same time.
Of course.
At the same time. Yeah, I know.
Together, yeah, obviously.
- Are you scared? - Of course I...
Scared?
Wow, really, Yoon Ha Na?
This is Yoon Ha Ru we're talking about.
Your big brother doesn't feel fear at all.
Honestly, I don't know what that word even means.
Your left leg has been shaking non-stop for the last few minutes.
Huh?
I'm not shaking.
I'm just getting the engine started.
What's it to you?
Why is the water... so pitch black?
It's making me imagine things lurking underneath the surface.
You sure have the ample imagination of the actress that you are.
This is an indoor pool.
There's nothing in the water.
And I have to tell you...
I'm a very good swimmer.
You know that I was in the children's swimming team.
Actually, I'm scared, too.
But...
As long as there's even a slim chance of hope,
I'd do anything.
Me too.
Because it's Jung Woo Jae.
Yeah.
My heart is racing.
Hold your breath, Yoon Ha Ru.
Got it.
Out of fear, or from excitement...
I'll never know for sure.
But I don't hesitate for even a moment...
as I dive into the emptiness below.
Into Jung Woo Jae.
Into you.
What's this?
What's going on?
What is happening?
What the...
What?
What is that?
That scared me!
Darn it, Yoon Ha Na!
You! What's up with this face? In the middle of the night, no less!
I thought I crossed the Styx or something!
Yoon Ha Ru?
Ah, I was preparing for an audition on this day.
The makeup looks pretty good.
It's captured the vibe well.
Oh, my heart.
It's 2010.
Are you serious?
This is the one, right?
The time machine?
December 31st, 2010...
That's the date of the second video.
We made it.
We actually traveled back in time?
Yes.
Wait, what?
Huh? What's wrong?
We're in some deep trouble, then.
Real deep trouble.
Why? What is it?
I am so gosh darn charmingly handsome.
Do you actually want to cross the Styx?
This skin...
No amount of product or treatment could ever recreate this.
This is the real thing, real baby-soft skin!
Get off me!
You are one unhinged bastard!
I should be the one on the big screen, not you.
It's Woo Jae!
What?
Meet me at the place at 11:20.
Wait for me!
Ugh, your hair is annoying! I should just chop it off!
You can cut it if you dare.
I'll fill up on grilled pork belly right before the national team trial,
so that you never pass the competition in the first place.
You'll never even bear the Taegeuk symbol.
Where are you even going?
I don't know.
It's too late to just walk off without a clear destination!
Well, Woo Jae wants to meet up! I can't just sit around doing nothing!
December 31st...
What were we doing that day?
Why did we meet up?
December... 31st...
It's the last day of the year, so...
- The beach! - The beach!
Wait, help me tie my hair up first!
I'm seriously going to cut it off!
I'm not bluffing!
He's not here.
Is this not the place?
No, it is.
This is the place, but...
It's past 11:50 now.
So why isn't he here?
Where are you, Jung Woo Jae?
Wait, I'll call him.
Hey, Ha Na.
Jung Woo Jae...
Jung Woo Jae, you bastard!
Jung Woo Jae, where the heck were you?
Where were you? Tell me!
We were supposed to meet in front of the campus, remember?
I was waiting for you, but you never came, so I came for you.
Why are you guys here?
Are you feeling okay?
No broken bones? No injuries?
I'm fine.
Hey. What's wrong with Ha Na?
What's up with you?
Three...
Two...
One! There it is.
Happy New Year, guys!
I guess.
Hey, what's going on with you, Yoon Ha Ru?
Why are you so unenthusiastic?
Oh, am I supposed to be doing something?
Well, no.
Not really, I guess.
This is so fun!
Yeah, guys!
Let's have a super happy new year! Lots of luck for everyone!
We're seniors now, seniors!
We're 19 years old now!
- What's up with Ha Na today? - This is so awesome!
I don't know.
She's acting a bit strange today.
Watch your step!
She's adorable.
- What? - She's...
No... nothing...
Ha Na. She's...
I said she's being particularly silly today.
See? It's ridiculous.
Something's up with her today.
She's just being so silly today.
Come on, this way!
Alright, alright!
Hey.
Keep it together, will you?
You're Yoon Ha Na now.
Yoon Ha Na, the world-famous actress, not the wild beast Yoon Ha Ru.
I know!
Woo Jae is giving you weird looks!
Stop acting like an imbecile!
Imbecile?
I'm the national judo team's treasure,
and the world's best judo player, Sir Yoon Ha Ru!
You should try your best to act like yourself,
and I as myself, don't you think?
Hey, you.
Are you embarrassed by me or something?
Of course I am, what kind of question is that? You're acting out of character in my body!
Besides...
I'm just scared.
What if some small action...
ends up irreversibly changing our past?
You know.
That's how it goes in movies.
Just think about how the medal changed.
We can save Jung Woo Jae.
Okay.
You must've been starving.
Hey, will you slow down?
All this food you're shoveling in your mouth right now...
are you even keeping track of how many calories that is?
This is my first meal of the day!
I'll just work out and burn it off, so stop nagging me!
You should slow down, though.
Here, drink some water, too.
Guys...
I need to use the toilet.
Agh, I'm about to poop my pants!
What, right now? It's dangerous in the dark.
- Do you want me to come with? - Stop talking, it's peeking out!
Ha Na!
What does he think he's doing?
Ha Na! That's the men's room!
No, no, I told you I'm not drunk!
I'm not drunk, I'm fine...
Stop there for a second.
All the toilets are backed up.
Everything's broken in there.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Did I poop too much? What if I clogged it?
I don't know what Jung Woo Jae is wishing for,
but whatever it is...
I wish for it to come true.
Please...
Please.
What did you wish for?
Hey! You're not supposed to tell.
It won't come true!
That's not how it works.
Come on, tell me. I could help make it come true.
Well, I suppose you could help, yeah.
What is it?
The national team trial is being held this year.
I want to make it on the team with you.
Yoon Ha Ru.
- Huh? - Well? Answer me.
Don't you want to?
- Well... - Of course!
Don't even worry about it!
You and I, we'll make it in. Whatever it takes.
Huh? Ha Na?
What do you mean, you and me?
Oh, no, no.
I meant, you and Yoon Ha Ru. You two.
You'll make it in.
You got me there.
About Woo Jae...
When did he stop judo again?
Right before the national team trial, so...
I guess around May?
He hurt his shoulder.
That's why he quit, right?
Did it happen during practice?
I think...
He just appeared with a cast on his arm one day.
Are you sure you're a good friend to him?
You're his friend, too, you know!
But you had no clue, either!
Well, this time around...
Let's figure that out first.
And then what?
That way, we can prevent it from happening.
That way...
he'll never have to quit judo.
- Let's go. - Yeah, let's go.
Okay.
[Our dream, a brighter 2011]
It's good.
Oh, you're back.
Wow, Woo Jae! How handsome you are!
What a charming young man!
Honey, what about me?
Am I charming, too?
I guess not.
Anyhow!
Did you guys enjoy the sunrise?
Did you take pictures?
Wash your hands, your dad made tteokguk.
- Mom! - Dad!
What is it now?
Don't you like it?
I did a good job on it.
No, it's not that.
I can't believe how the two of you look!
This is unreal!
This is just...
Mom, your skin!
Holy moly guacamole, that's gnarly!
What did you say? Hole-y? Mole-y?
And what, gnarled?
Not you too, Ha Na!
No, Mom! It's a compliment! A compliment!
Yoon Ha Na, come here!
I said come here!
Did you take after Ha Ru?
Huh? Come here!
- Mom, Mom! - How dare you call me gnarled!
- It's a compliment! - Come here right now!
- No, I was complimenting you! - It's a compliment...
Eat up, everyone.
Woah, it's gosh dang tummylicious!
Yoon Ha Na!
What do you mean by that now?
It means it's really good.
It's just what we say.
Yeah, that's right.
- Is this true? - Yes.
Come on, honey.
It's just how kids are.
We were young once, too, right?
It's just how teens talk. Their lingo.
They'll grow out of it.
"Grow out of it?"
You still say stuff like rad and bonkers.
- Old habits die hard, and... - Oh, look, meat fritters.
Your favorite, see?
Aw, you look lovely when you eat.
It tastes great, yes.
- Dad. - Yes?
This is an amazing meal.
Well, I am a good cook, see?
What do you guys think? Am I rad?
Yeah, radical!
Bonkers!
Ha Ru, did you finish packing yet?
Packing? For what?
Hey, Yoon Ha Ru.
You're leaving for the training camp in two days!
I told you to get ready beforehand!
You never listen, do you?
Hurry up and finish eating! You need to pack!
Honey, calm down and have another fritter...
Oh, you've already got one.
You should tell me right away if you changed your number.
Son. Where are you?
[Haesol High Judo Team Winter Camp] Attention!
There is only one goal in this winter training camp.
You are not only a team on the mat.
You will eat, sleep, and even use the toilet... as if you are one single organism.
Therefore, you will stay in rooms of four. No exceptions.
- Oh, crap. - Any objections?
- No, sir! - No, sir!
Good. Now, take off to unpack and settle in. You will return here after 30 minutes.
Understood?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
We're in the same room.
Oh, okay...
Us, too.
Hey, Yoon Ha Na.
Listen up carefully.
Where you will be going tomorrow is no ordinary training camp.
That place is like the wilderness. A safari, if you will.
A safari?
But do not fear!
For I, your big brother, will teach you all the essentials of survival.
First off.
The smell.
Smell?
The moment you set foot in that room...
you will learn what hell is like.
You've got to be exaggerating.
You know Han Soo Hyuk, right?
Han Soo Hyuk?
The guy who quit judo and came to my university...
That Han Soo Hyuk?
Well? What about him?
What does he have to do with this?
If you are condemned to a room with him...
Well, you truly are doomed.
[Alarms off, please!]
[Han Soo Hyuk] [Yoon Ha Ru]
What's wrong?
He has rhinitis, so his nose is always stuffy, and he can't smell very well.
Maybe that's why, but...
You!
When did you last wash your uniform?
Hey.
Want a bite?
He doesn't do his laundry.
As you already know, however...
He's a good kid.
It's good bread.
And now.
Pyo Gyeong Woo.
I know Gyeong Woo.
He's the son of the master of that training center we went to as children.
Starting tomorrow, your eyes will be forced to witness...
the parade of muscles.
"Parade of muscles?"
- Get it out of my face. - But it's really good.
What...
What are you doing?
Hey.
Pyo Gyeong Woo, sir, reporting today's sick gains.
- What's going on? - How do you like them?
Our dear Gyeong Woo is, how should I say this?
He's like a big dog who likes praise.
Just think of him as that.
He's a good kid, too. He doesn't mean any harm.
Here, my external oblique. Feel it.
Come on, won't you feel it?
My rectus abdominis...
I've been doing low-rises...
Salute!
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Also,
this is the most important of them all.
There's more?
Jung Woo Jae.
Keep an eye on him.
If he's secretive, dig deeper.
If he says he's fine, don't believe him.
This time...
We need to figure it out faster than him.
Okay.
Got it?
Yeah.
Are you done packing?
What good is that going to do?
Don't take hour-long showers while you're there, understood?
I just take longer showers than most, okay?
Take stuff like this, for working out.
You can keep this stuff for yourself.
This time...
I swear I'll protect you, Jung Woo Jae.
[Haesol High Judo Team Winter Camp]
Agh, what are you doing?
Jung Woo Jae...
Hey, Yoon Ha Ru!
Get it together!
[Quitters are never winners!]
Your skills... are getting better!
It's getting better by the minute! Good!
- What a monster! - That must be stressful.
You're getting better!
Come on, believe it!
It's like a whole truck is on top of you.
This is how you learn, you hear me?
This is how you learn!
Look, guys, Woo Jae is having a great workout sesh!
Yoon Ha Ru!
You've got that glint in your eyes.
Come here.
Come on, hurry up.
Looks refreshing.
- You have to go. - No, but...
- Hurry up. - You have no choice.
- Quickly, now. - Goodbye.
- Hurry, now. - Good luck!
Yoon Ha Ru.
What is wrong with you?
Get out of here.
Hey, Jung Woo Jae.
Are you alright?
What were you thinking?
What's the matter?
- Did I do something wrong? - You just got pummeled into the ground!
He armlocked you!
What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean? I'm training.
Are you injured?
Move your shoulder like this. Does it hurt?
Hey, look, I'm fine!
Hey!
Take good care of your shoulder!
Just be gentle with it, okay?
- Wait, what's wrong? - Are you hurt?
- Where? - Is something wrong?
I'm fine.
- Get out of my way. - Hey, but your shoulder...
He's clearly injured...
Right?
What, is this seriously all you're eating?
Yes. What's wrong?
This isn't enough food for an athlete.
I think it's perfect.
What's up with you, man?
No, why do you ask?
Nothing.
[Dad]
Hey.
Oh, wow, hello!
Hi! Hi, everyone.
Let's see...
Here.
What's this, Ms. Ha Na?
Have a sip before your meal.
You drink this, and your energy just bursts through the roof!
No more tiredness! Bam! It's the good stuff, I swear.
This is what makes a national athlete.
National athlete? Who?
Oh, that's...
There's a person I know. National athlete and gold medalist.
- No matter, drink it, come on. - There's a person, you hear?
If she says there's a guy, there's a guy.
- You'll see when you try it! - What is it?
What is it, huh?
Woo Jae.
- Me? - Drink up.
I'm at the school. Come outside.
So tasty!
Hey! Son!
Son, hey! Come here!
There are too many people around. Come with me.
Wow, the bastard.
So rude to his own father.
- Where are they going? - I don't know.
My son. It's so hard to see you these days.
How did you find out about this place?
What? How did I find out?
You know my friend, Mr. Jung Gyu, right?
Well, he told me you were in the newspaper!
See this? "The future of Korea.
Rising stars of the national team..."
And here, here. Look.
"Haesol High, Judo Team, 11th grader...
Jung Woo Jae."
Now, isn't that something?
Wow, so, whose son is that, I wonder?
Am I right?
So, where's your mom?
Why do you want to know?
"Why?"
So I'm just supposed to let that fox live happily ever after without me?
I don't know.
We haven't kept in touch for a while.
You little liar.
You go and tell that woman, you hear me?
Tell her that she'll never hide from me.
I'll find her, just you wait.
And you.
Got some cash?
The article said you're getting good financial support.
Nothing? Really?
Do you think I owe you anything?
Think, now. Have you ever given me anything?
- That's no way to talk to your dad! - "Dad?"
If you want me to treat you like a father,
don't ever go looking for Mom.
I'm warning you.
That's everything I have.
So just please,
don't ever come see me again.
Rude little rascal.
See you.
- Why are you making weird noises? - This is a good stretch!
- Come on, faster. - Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Let's do 10 sets of 400.
- Boo! - No!
- What even! - Boo! Boo!
Okay, then, 15 sets it is.
- 10 sets is good! - Yay, 10! We'll do our best!
- All good? - Yes, sir!
If Soo Hyuk falls behind, I'll make all of you do 4 more sets,
so keep encouraging him, okay?
I'll carry him on my back!
- Pass it on. - Ready, set...
This is nice.
Do you think I owe you anything?
Have you ever given me anything?
- That's no way to talk to your dad! - "Dad?"
If you want me to treat you like a father,
don't ever go looking for Mom.
Time for exercise.
I can't do anything with Yoon Ha Na's feeble body!
What am I supposed to do in this body?
Think, Yoon Ha Ru.
What can I do in this situation?
Come up with something, anything, Yoon Ha Ru!
- Bye! - Goodbye!
- What are we having? - Pork belly!
- Grilled pork belly! - Pork belly, pork, pork!
Hey, what are you doing? Come out already!
I'm coming, okay? I think the makchang I had was bad.
I got a bellyache.
You're pissing me off.
It's out of my system now.
- Hey, Woo Jae, do you have time to... - Oh!
The walking 500 million won.
- Woo Jae... - Hey! Come to the back gate!
Back gate?
Okay, on it!
Hey! Stop right there, money-maker!
Hey!
Hey! Come here!
Why are there so many damn stairs?
[Location information act]
"Threatening for money is extortion, a criminal offense..."
"Tracking someone's location is against the law..."
So it's a felony, huh?
You go and tell that woman, you hear me?
Tell her that she'll never hide from me.
Oh, I'll find her, just you wait.
And you.
Got some cash?
Can he file a restraining order or something?
[Ask a lawyer online]
[Underage son...]
[Beast]
Wow, that's rich.
Yes, this is the mangy beast speaking.
So, what did you find out?
Woo Jae...
Woo Jae is...
Well? Spit it out! What's wrong with Woo Jae?
You little...
I'm here.
Where are you?
I lost them.
They're nowhere to be seen!
I'm certain they went this way!
Some sketchy men said Woo Jae is worth 500 million won.
They were chasing him around, and...
What do we do?
- Yoon Ha Na. - Yes?
Listen carefully.
Haesol is a small city. We'll find them sooner or later.
Okay.
Damn it!
Come here, you little rat!
Come here!
Get out of the way!
Get over here!
Stop there, you bastard!
Oh, sir!
You're dead now.
It's been a while, huh?
How did you find me this time?
How did I find you?
Well, the answer's obvious, isn't it?
Your dad, of course!
He literally pointed me to where you are.
I...
I don't want anything to do with him.
- Just let me go. - Wow, just wow.
You're an athlete, right?
You're well-recognized, too, isn't that so?
I heard you receive good sponsorship.
- That's not true. - Don't lie to me.
Your dad was boasting all about it.
He said you'll be the one to pay us back.
So?
How will you repay us?
Why would I pay for his debt?
Why? Because your dad told us to collect from you!
Okay?
If you're so talented, surely you get sponsorships and scholarships.
So there's all that money.
I wonder if you get bonuses for winning tournaments?
Then we'll have to support him so that he can keep winning, isn't that right?
Make sure no one else wins, you get me?
Well, then, sir.
Should we break the whole Judo team's legs?
- Shut up. - What did you say, you little mongrel?
Oh, look who's mad.
Don't lay a finger on our judo team.
So you really cherish your team, huh?
Little boy.
I guess you're too young to understand this,
but you just told me your greatest weakness.
Get it now?
- How dare you! - Back down.
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down.
Oh, you silly boy.
You're just full of surprises, aren't you?
Get a load of this guy!
Oh, just wait and see. Stop copying my move!
You little...
Oh, this guy's funny.
- Hey, hey. Loosen up. - Let him go.
- He's falling a bit short. - Let go.
Oh, god damn it!
- What are you guys standing around for? - I said let go!
- Scared me there for a second. - You little bastard!
- Stay down! - Let me at him, too!
- I'll kill you! Die! Die! - Stop blocking!
Hey, guys.
- Let him stand. - Yes, sir.
- Get up, bastard. - Stand up.
You're dead now, little rat.
Hold him there. Hold tight.
You bastard...
Sir!
- What the... - Who the hell are you?
How dare you!
Hey! Are you alright?
Why are you here?
It doesn't matter. Who are these people?
Hey, you two. Mr. Skinny and Mr. Bald.
Just who are you guys?
I'm not Mr. Bald. I'm Real Love Capital's Department Manager!
I'm not Mr. Skinny. I'm the Team Leader of Real Love Capital!
Capital? Real Love?
Wow, that's an awful name.
I'll take skinny, you take the bald one. Got it?
- Okay. - Come here, you!
Ow, owie... blood...
- I'm bleeding! - Sir?
Blood! I'm bleeding!
I'm bleeding out! It's all sticky!
Blood?
This is sweat, sir!
Sweat?
Hey!
- Hey! - But it hurts!
It's sweat, sir!
I think my skull's fractured!
They're running away!
Ugh, Mommy... Mo-om!
I have an ouchie...
I'm about to lose it.
Where are you, Jung Woo Jae?
Did you find him?
Yeah.
He's with me right now, so you go on and head back to the dormitory.
- Okay. - Bye.
This is the worst.
What is?
I really...
didn't want you to see this.
What are you talking about, you bastard? What does it matter?
- Bastard? - Are you...
Are you embarrassed?
Okay. Let me tell you something.
Get this. Actually...
I peed my pants in 2nd grade.
Okay.
What?
It was sports day.
The waiting line for the restroom was so long.
I waited and waited, but it just wasn't getting any shorter.
It's a secret, okay? Nobody knows this.
Yeah, of course I'll keep it a secret.
So we're even?
Or is this not enough? You want to know something worse?
No, no.
I think I'm good.
If I'm being honest...
My dad is a real piece of work.
I thought it all ended when I moved here,
but I guess I can't really run from it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to vent.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
Thank you.
Thanks for telling me.
This is the perfect time for some soju.
Ha Na, you...
Do you drink?
No, dummy.
What I mean is, we should have a drink together once we turn 20.
- Oh, okay. - Dummy!
- Let's go! - Okay.
Go inside.
Your parents must be worried.
Hey, Jung Woo Jae.
Spend the night with me in my room.
What? S-spend the night?
- With you? - Yeah.
But...
Your parents are home.
I can't possibly stay the night in your room, Ha Na.
Oh, no, I meant Ha Ru's room.
Spend the night over in Yoon Ha Ru's room.
They won't let you in the dorm now, so...
- Yeah, you're right. - Yeah.
Let's head in.
Okay.
What was I even thinking?
Get it together!
I want soboro bread...
Get me some soboro bread...
Jung Woo Jae slept over at our place.
He was gone when I woke up.
Is he at the dormitory?
Yes?
Good morning, sir.
This is Woo Jae's locker, right?
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
Wait, what are you doing? That's his stuff.
He withdrew the deposit for the dormitory and is moving out.
He's quitting judo.
Wait, what?
Why won't you answer, Jung Woo Jae?
What could possibly have happened?
Hey, four bowls for breakfast is too much!
What?
Where's all the stuff gone?
Did he leave?
I don't know.
What's this camcorder doing here?
[Yoon Ha Na]
Out of battery...
Hey, turn the air conditioning on.
How does that sound?
Yoon Ha Ru, answer the phone!
[Yoon Ha Na]
What?
I'm back home... all of a sudden?
[May 25th, Monday] The award ceremony...
is tomorrow?
[Woo Jae]
[No results]
The number you have reached is not in service.
- What? - Yes.
- What? They're releasing an article? - Boss?
On the day before the award ceremony? Those snakes.
Ha Na's schedule will go as we planned.
I'm... me.
I'm back.
As soon as the revised complaint is ready,
I don't care if it's in the middle of the night, just email me.
Don't forget to CC me.
Good.
[Yoon Ha Na]
Where are you?
I'm at the company. Ye Rang's office.
Get over here right now.
Huh? Where are you?
The award ceremony is tomorrow. Where would I be other than at home?
Ah, right, okay!
I'll be there in a second.
You're leaving me in the middle of a date?
Did I just hear that right?
Or did you seriously lose all your common sense, Yoon Ha Ru?
No, it's not that, I mean, it's...
Well?
Is there someone new who's willing to take the lead?
No, I swear it's nothing like that.
But, yeah, she does take the lead, I guess.
How am I supposed to take this, Yoon Ha Ru?
Lovingly?
I mean...
It's just Ha Na.
Huh?
What's up with Ha Na? Do you want me to come with?
I'll call you when I get there!
Love you!
[Woo Jae is missing in both the past and the present. What went wrong?]
No, no.
My friend, Woo Jae.
[Water triggers it? Not just the Ha Na and Ha Ru, but the camcorder needs to be wet, too]
[How does the camcorder choose the specific time to travel to? Is it random?]
What do you mean, you don't know him?
Darling, did you have too much wine?
I checked the whole list of employees at the security agency.
But I found nobody with the name Jung Woo Jae.
Alright, then. I'll call you back later.
Okay.
She says she doesn't know Woo Jae.
Just how much did we change this time?
Will this actually help us find the pattern?
Are you sure about it?
You and I, together, with the camcorder, fall into a body of water.
That's what triggers the time travel.
And the time we travel to...
is based on the videos kept in the camcorder's memory.
But as for the rules...
I don't know.
Maybe the camcorder decides?
What?
Think about it.
Maybe there is no other rule, except for the diving part.
Maybe it's just on the camcorder's whims...
So it's randomized, maybe?
Well, I can't say you're absolutely wrong.
I like it when things are simple.
This camcorder is giving me a headache.
The award ceremony is tomorrow.
Yeah, it is.
He... will be there.
The ceremony...
Are you going?
- I have to. - Don't even think about it!
What if he really does show up?
It's fine because we know he'll be there.
That way, I can avoid him.
Or maybe even catch him.
No, you can't. It's too dangerous.
I know.
I'm sure Woo Jae's alive somewhere.
Let's get that bastard tomorrow and go find Woo Jae.
Then...
Just promise me one thing.
Tomorrow, at the ceremony,
whatever happens there...
promise me you'll put yourself first.
To me, what matters the most tomorrow is saving you.
You'll have to be alive to find Woo Jae.
Understood?
Yes.
[Baekryong Film Awards]
[Congratulations on the award, Actress Yoon Ha Na]
Have a nice day.
Right now,
the clock reads half past six.
The award goes to...
Yoon Ha Na, from "I Was There in Your Night."
Congratulations.
The ceremony ends at 11.
Everyone's leaving. Let's go.
The time frame in which Woo Jae and I were together in the waiting room...
Hey, Jung Woo Jae.
[Seok Min] is roughly between 11:30 and 11:40.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
He's so handsome!
Five hours from now...
Someone...
will be pointing a knife at me.
Thank goodness...
You're not here to protect me this time,
but I've returned to this moment.
Don't be scared.
Just be yourself.
You're not here to keep me safe today.
But I...
I will survive, no matter what...
[Actress Yoon Ha Na]
[Congratulations on the award, Actress Yoon Ha Na]
And I will save you.
Jung Woo Jae.
What is this?
The scar on his arm.
I know I saw it.
Let's go back again.
We can find him.
How much does he owe in total?
You said you'd pay me back for today.
Korea's national team judo player, Jung Woo Jae!
Win the gold.
Something's off.
Something's really off.
Yoon Ha Na?
Jung Woo Jae, get up.
You saw the way he looked at me, right?
It was so intense, I thought I'd melt!